the British gave us
нам британцы поставили
Zelensky, he is Well, you know his
Зеленского он же Ну ты знаешь его
real name No,
настоящая фамилия Нет
Greenfields, no one voted What
гринфилдс никто не голосовал Какие
elections Well, you would know how elections are made in Russia
выборы Ну ты же в России бы знаешь как
Hello What are we talking about, about war Where are you from
Здравствуйте О чём говорим о войне Вы
again, war Where are you
опять война Вы
Russia, I can see it in your face city
России я вижу по лицу город
What does this mean
Какой это имеет значение
Yes, I talk about one thing with Muscovites, there is another with
Да с москвичами об одном говорю там с
Vladivostok A
Владивосток о
Muscovite from
другом Москвич из
Penza understood how you feel about the fact that
пенз понял как относитесь к тому что
Russia is at war with Ukraine,
Россия воюет с Украиной
how do you
как
feel Well, in principle, it is not
отнош Ну и в принципе не
positive But
положительно А
how, well, look, let's say I will say that
как ну вот смотрите допустим я скажу что
in any case it is
в любом случае
negative the question is what is being
отрицательно вопрос вопрос в том что кае
persecuted and is it my fault, let's say,
преследуется и не виноват ли допустим я
or my neighbor, figuratively speaking, who, let's
или мой сосед образно который который
say, is not involved in
допустим не причастен к
this Well, in any case, it is negative
этому Ну в любом случае отрицательно это
in any case, and what do you think is the
в любом случае а как вы считаете из-за
reason for the war?
из-за
Well, most likely, let's say, they did not
чего Ну скорее всего что-то допустим не
share something and now they have started And who is to
поделили и вот у них началось А кто
blame for this
тогда виноват в этой
war then, I don't even know if it is to blame
войне я не знаю даже может быть виноват
Well, someone, probably, someone Who is who
Ну кто-то же наверное кто-то Кто кто Вот
This could not be shared Who is to blame, who, what are
это не смог поделить Кто виноват кто что
you saying Well, the war has begun
вы что говорите Ну вот война началась
because something was not divided, then
из-за того что что-то не поделили значит
someone who did not divide it is to blame
вот кто-то кто это не поделил он виноват
Who is this
Кто этот
to blame No, it can't be They wanted to
виноваты Нет ну не может быть хотели
divide something, let's say figuratively, and they did
поделить что-то допустим образно и у них
n't succeed, and so who is to
не получилось и так да у кого у них то
blame, who is to blame in this war
кто виноват кто виноват в этой войне
Well, I think there are two
Ну я думаю две
sides Well, with whom is it fighting and who is fighting Well, who is who
стороны Ну с кем воюет и кто воюет Ну
Voice the guilty people Name the people
кто кто Озвучь людей виноватых Назови
Ukraine and Russia are fighting correctly So who
Украина и Россия воют правильно Так кто
attacked whom No, you mean if we
напал Не ну вы имеете в виду если
consider that
считать то
who invaded if so it
что кто вторгся если так этом
invaded then who is to
вторглась то кто
blame Well, it wasn't just that it
виноват Ну она же не просто так
invaded
вторглась
Correct, I don't know, it's just not simple Maybe she has
Правильно не знаю просто не просто Может
Wait, how else are
у не Подожди а как по по-другому
these problems solved
решаются эти проблемы
if I look, if I invaded your
если я смотри если я вторгся в вашу
apartment for the police Who is to blame, I am to
квартиру для полиции Кто виноват я
blame if Russia invaded a foreign
виноват если Россия вторглась в чужую
country Who is to blame No, if a person
страну Кто виноват Не ну если человек
doesn't understand in words how else,
словами не понимает как по-другому
let's say, it is solved Well, how are such matters
допустим решается ну как вот такие дела
solved, let's say How what Well, let's
решаются допустим Как какие
say, let's say,
Ну вот допустим вот сейчас допустим
America, Russia, what did Russia not divide,
Америка поди Россия что не поделила
that Russia invaded
Россия с Украиной что Россия вторглась в
Ukraine, we divided Belarus  Do I
Украину мы делили Беларусь я правильно
understand correctly that Ukraine and Russia divided
понимаю что Украина и Россия делили
Belarus, they couldn't divide it, they didn't
Беларусь не смогли поделить не
agree, and Russia invaded
договорились и Россия вторглась в
Ukraine? And how much is Belarus? Well, what did we divide?
Украину А почем Беларусь Ну а что что мы
Well, you want to say for nothing
делили Не ну вы хотите сказать поничем
Russia WTO is for you, I'm asking Why did
Россия ВТО для вас спрашиваю Для чего
Russia invade, what did they divide, what did it invade?
Россия вторглась что они поделили что
Well, again, official
она вторглась не Ну опять же официальные
What does it
Какие
mean that infringes on Russians? Well,
получается то что ущемляет русских Ну
Russian-speaking people? It's just that if it infringes on them, they
русскоязычных Просто если ущемляет они
could, for example, leave or
же могли бы допустим уехать бы или
something. Yes, they would have left. And why did
как-то да да они бы Уехали да А зачем
Russia invade Ukraine? Well, explain
Россия вторглась в Украину Ну объясни
what they divided?
что они поделили
What does it mean, Crimea? Anya, they divided Crimea, they
Что ну получается Крым Ани поделили Крым
wanted to take Crimea. And in the end, who
хотели забрать Крым Да и в итоге по кто
wanted to take Crimea? Russia, yes, we didn't just not divide it. Well, we
хотел забрать Крым Россия да то мы не то
should. That's right, they didn't
что не поделили Ну надо Правильно не
divide it, when, for example,
поделили когда вот например живёт
Ukraine lives, Russia lives. And here is some
Украина живёт Россия А тут какой-то
no-man's-land, and Ukraine and Russia want to
ничейный остров и Украина и Россия хотят
divide it, but they didn't divide it, they didn't
его делить но не поделили не
agree. Yes, I understand that. They didn't
договорились Да это я понимаю Не
divide it. And here Crimea is part of Ukraine.
поделили А тут Крым - это часть Украины
We didn't divide it. Russia attacked Ukraine
Мы её не делили Россия напала на Украину
and seized Crimea, that's what it should be called. Well,
и захватила Крым так надо называть Ну
okay, fine. That's what you mean.  in any case Horseshoe in
ладно хорошо Вот вы по-любому Подкова
any case you know If you why then
по-любому знаете Если вы для чего тогда
Russia the second What goals did
Россия втор Какие цели преследовал
Russia pursue as an imperialist state Yes
Россия империалистической государство Да
wants to seize Ukraine Well, it turns out that the
хочет захватить Украину Да ну Получается
USSR was part of it Ukraine
же СССР в составе же она была Украина
it didn't go there to Poland or there to
она же не пошла там на Польшу или там на
Lithuania Why why exactly Ukraine it
Литву Почему почему именно Украину она
went because of
пошла из-за
what Yes because Russia Russia wants to
чего Да потому что Россия Россия хочет
restore the USSR first of all wants to
восстановить СССР в первое дело хочет
seize Ukraine Well it's not just like that it
Украину захватить Ну не просто так же на
went to Ukraine right and why and
Украину пошла правильно а почему а
why Well why not to Kazakhstan Well why why do
почему Ну почему не на Казахстан Ну
I think that it's just like that it
почему почему я считаю что просто
just doesn't happen probably like it doesn't
так ну просто так не бывает наверно как
happen Russia here drunk Putin woke up
не бывает Россия вот проснулся пьяный
and said Let's go to
Путин и говорит Давайте пойдём на
Ukraine he's an old senile man he's
Украину он старый маразматик он
mentally ill Well and why is Ukraine
психически больной Да а почему Украина
not to blame that it was attacked the one
же не виновата что на неё напали тот на
who was attacked is never to blame it's all a
кого напали никогда не виноват это всё
base
база
if you were attacked then it's not you who is to blame but the one
если на тебя напали то виноват не ты а
who attacked it was like that from
тот кто напал это ж так было и спокон
time immemorial it's written in the law and in the statute it
веков так в законе написано и в статуте
happens and reasons for a person if the right
бывает же и причины на человека если
attacks What reasons Well so What
нападает пра Какие причины Ну так Какие
reasons voice the reasons why Russia
причины озвучити причины почему Россия
attacked
напала на
Ukraine  Well, I'm saying that
Украину вот я же говорю
if you think about it, as they say,
ещё если подумать так как говорят там
it's territory there, Well, there's enough territory in Russia,
это территория Ну территории то в России
Why did Russia
хватает Да зачем Россия на Зачем твоя
attack
страна напала на
Ukraine? I'm not saying that, as
Украину не я же говорю если как говорят
yours say, I watched the blog, as you do, look at me, It
ваши Я смотрел бло как ты смотри как мне
doesn't matter who, As they say, I asked you,
Неважно кто Как говорит я у тебя спросил
tell me what you think, Why did Russia attack
скажи как ты думаешь Зачем Россия напала
Ukraine? Well, most likely, they did
Украину Ну скорее всего на условия
n't want to agree on Russia's terms and everything,
России не хотели договариваться и всё
agree on what,
договариваться о чём
Well, the fact that America and
Ну то что приближается Америка и
NATO troops are approaching, Well, that's also stupid, I
натовские войска Ну это тоже глупо Я
think,
думаю
Yes, I understand correctly, You
да я правильно понимаю Ты правильно
understand correctly that this is stupid, Yes, what were the
понимаешь что это глупо да то какие были
conditions, Because of what, Russia, let's
условия из-за чего Россия давай
get to it, we've almost gotten to the bottom of the
доберёмся мы уже почти докопались до
truth, Why did Russia attack Ukraine? Why did
истины Почему Россия напала на Украину
it happen there, what did they agree on,
Почему что она там что они договорились
What were the conditions, What is happening about the World Cup,
Какие условия что вообще о ЧМ происхо
what is happening in this
что делается в этой
life, Well, initially, there was the seizure of Crimea,
жизни Ну изначально был захват э Крыма
Crimea, Well, why did Russia take and
Крыма Да ну зачем Россия взяла и
seize Crimea, Well, again, it's clear that
захватила Крым Ну опять же понятно что
it
она как
was like, well, under Ukraine, yes, Well,
бы у ну под Украиной была образом да Ну
again, they gave it, she wanted to take, Well,
опять же подарили она хотела взять Ну
gifts, gifts, not gifts, This is from childhood,
подарки подарки не отдарки Это с детства
We all know, gifts, not gifts, everything was given,
Мы все знаем подарки не отдарки всё
This is ours, Bazaar, no, no  Well, if you
подарили это наше Базару нет не Ну
gave it, you can take it back. In
подарили то можно и Обратно забрать по
theory, no, gifts are not gifts in return. This is the
идее нет подарки не отдарки это это
basis. If I give it as a gift. I can take
база если я дарственно делаю Я же могу
it back later. If you gave it, it has already
её обратно потом если ты подарил это уже
become the person's. You took it from the person. The
стало у человека всё забрал у человек
person was offended. And ok. No, you can't take it back. This is
человек обиделся да и ладно нет нет
all, actually, the
забрать нельзя это уже всё это
person. Everything. Why did you attack Ukraine? I do
собственно человека всё то зачем вы
n't know. I
Украину Я не знаю на
can't answer. Then if you don't
не могу ответить то тогда если ты не
know. Why are you saying that Ukraine is
знаешь Зачем же ты говоришь что Украина
also to blame. Well, in any case, it is guilty.
тоже виновата Ну в любом случае винова
Why stop. You don't know why, but you
Почему стоп ты не знаешь почему но
say that in any case, it is to blame. What kind of
говоришь в любом случае она виновата что
joke? Well, it can't be one
за прикол Ну же не может быть один
person. That's how you say. Putin is a brainless
человек вот как Говорите Путин без мозго
person. And why can't he? Why not?
пошл и А почему не может Почему не вот
Hitler also attacked the USSR. The SS is
Гитлер также Гитлер напал на СССР СС же
not to blame. Hitler is to blame. It's true.
не виноват виноват Гитлер
Well, there was a seizure of territory.
Правда Ну там был захват территори
In theory, it would be
ми По идее как бы
Hitler's to blame. Hitler is to blame. He
так виноват Гитлер виноват Гитлер он же
attacked. Stalin is not to blame. It's true that
напал Сталин не виноват же правда и
Ukraine is not to
Украина не
blame either. But again, Lenin was also, let's say.
виновата но Ленин опять же тоже был
Lenin was a puppet. Whose
допустим тоже Как марионеткой Ленин Чья
puppet was
марионетка
he? Well, he traveled to Europe a lot and issued
был ну он же много и в Европу ездил и
decrees there. It's like these decrees weren't there.
указы там это же как бы не было эти
Tell me.  I wonder Whose
указы Расскажи мне интересно Чья он был
puppet was he Well wasn't he a puppet Whose
марионетка Ну не был разве марионеткой
puppet was Lenin
чей Чья марионетка был Ленин на поезде
they took him on a train somewhere I don't remember or some
проводили куда я не помню то ли какие-то
I don't remember Now why let's do it this
я не помню Сейчас уже это почему давай
way Lenin is a puppet of the Anglo-Saxons Germans
так Ленин марионетка англосаксов немцев
Swiss
швейцарцев
whose Well the Anglo-Saxons most likely that is
чей Ну англосаксов скорее всего у то
Lenin is a puppet of the
есть Ленин марионетка
Anglo-Saxons Well it turns out it turns out
англосаксов Ну получается
it's these Rothschilds all sorts of
получается вот этих ротшильдов всяких
Rottweilers
ротвейлеров
Well it doesn't come from you
Да ну не от тебя он двигался по-любому
anyway Yeah it does it turns out If Lenin is a puppet of the
Угу то получается Если Ленин марионетка
Anglo-Saxons And Lenin created the USSR then the
англосаксов А Ленин создал СССР значит
Anglo-Saxons created the USSR Well the USSR
англосаксы создали СССР Ну ССР же
was originally a project they didn't know about it no no What kind of project was it
был проект не знали об этом нет нет Что
unification so And whose project was it
обединение так А чей это был
I can't remember exactly now
проект я сейчас точно не могу вспомнить
you're just asking such topics now I'm
вы просто такие темы сечас задаёте не
interested you're a very thinking
мне интересно вот вы очень мыслящий
person I like to meet
человек Я люблю встречать чат рулетки
smart people chat roulette then tell me what kind of project the
умных людей то расскажите что за проект
USSR was no I'm definitely not a smart person
был СССР не Я не умный человек
Well I
однозначно Ну я
have
имею
some such Wok talk on Su they would
каких-то такие Вок гово по Су
tell me that I could pick up
рассказали бы что я мог бы подхватить и
this and that But that  what as if you want to prove
это А вот то что как бы вы меня хотите
your version of me, let's say
свою версию допустим
Tell me why then
доказать Скажите почему тогда
Russia is under me about the SR Who created the USSR, the
Россия подо меня про СР Кто создал ССР
Americans, the British, who I don't know the language I
американцы бриты кто я не знаю говор Я
watched the
смотрел
document
докумен
prop not on my own, he moved there, there were many
проп не от себя двигался там его много
who
кто
covered him up again Whose version is this I don't
прикрывал опять же Это чья версия Я не
know, you understand, well,
знаю понимаете это ну по телевизору
let's say I watched it on TV, it was a long time ago
допустим смотрел я яже давно это было
already Yeah
уже
Quite interesting And what do you think,
Угу Довольно интересно А как ты считаешь
uh, if Lenin created the USSR and it was
ээ если Ленин создал СССР и это был
someone's foreign project, then the USSR is
чей-то иностранный проект то СССР - это
evil Well,
зло Ну почему сразу зло допустим Ну
why is it
почему
evil right away, let's say Well, why is it evil No, well, let's say, I don't know
зло Нет ну вот допустим вот я не знаю
figuratively, something is created by someone by what kind of people
образно что-то кто-то какими людьми
and somehow Yes, but this doesn't
создаётся и как-то образом Да но это же
mean evil or it's bad, but in any
не значи зло или это плохо но же в любом
case, it's done under some kind of, well, I don't
случае это делается под каким-то там ну
know all the rules, all the decrees there,
я не знаю все правила все указы там
some kind of this again
какие-то это же опять же
Well, you have
Ну вы
educational
образовани
abilities, I don't know in what way do you
способности я я не знаю в каких вы
measure all this What do you think, above
мерите это всё Как вы считаете выше
average, average, below
среднего средний ниже
average Well, probably average, I
среднего Ну наверное средний я так
think so, average, I understood, well, a pretty
думаю средний понял ну довольно
realistic assessment, I agree, I just do
реалистическая оценка согласен просто я
n't know how it's measured and
как бы не знаю как это измеряется и
it depends on who you communicate with And  how is it all the same well Yes
смотря с кем общаться И как это всё же
it is not known that if you know I do not
Да это не знае что если вы знаете я не
know So I as if for whom did you vote
знаю Значит я как бы за кого голосовали
in the elections never Vote once
на выборах никогда не Голосова один раз
I am 18 years old I was interested I voted
я 18 лет мне было интересно я голосовал
for Zhirinovsky that's all more
за Жириновского вот и всё больше Это в
What
каком
year do you want to know my age or how
году хотите узнать мой возраст или как
Yes 35 I am 35 years old
Да 35 мне лет 35 лет
Pony it turns out
Поня это получается
2008 it turns out yes
2008 получается да
cool
прикольно
goal put I say Putin this is for
гол пути говорю Путин это за
Zhirinovsky I liked the
Жириновского мне нравился
challenge again this is also an incomprehensible
вызывание опять же это тоже непонятно
statement I am still thinking why they did
высказывание я и сейчас думаю почему его
n't kill him then for such statements
тогда не убивали за такие высказывания
this is very interesting for him there would be
это очень интерес него бы
challenges
вызывания
pony children said such things there but this is
пони дест такие вот там говорил но это
also how he spoke as
вот тоже так он разговаривал как
if ambiguously and as if and in the end he kind of
бы двояко вроде и как бы а в итоге он
got away from it beautifully Well so it
как бы от этого уходил красиво Ну так
turns out Zhirinovsky you can
так получается Жириновский можете
say when he
сказать когда он
Putin Well in principle he did not say but he
Путина Ну в принципе не говорил но он
said Paul him Yes these are such I
говорил Поль него Да это такие бы
understand M
понимаю М
say Zhirinovsky he was for Putin
говори Жириновский он был за Путина по
essentially yes that is he was the party in power I
сути да то есть он был партия власти я
think everyone there is for Putin in any case
думаю там все за Путина в любом случае
this definitely does not happen I think the
однозначно такого не бывает Я думаю так
same with you listen to me a question like this
же у вас слушайте мне вопрос такой вот у
you had Saakashvili yes
вас был же Саакашвили да
yes he Who was the governor or who
да он Кем был губернатором или кто он
was he in Odessa or who was he there we don't have
был в Одесе или кто он там был у нас
provinces therefore there are no
нету губерний поэтому нет
governors of the MR there or whoever you have there I
губернаторов МР там или кто у вас там я
don't know the head of the regional state
не знаю главой областной государственной
administration And how did he even get there that's how they
администрации А как он туда вообще попал
appointed him no well they appointed him
вот как назначили его не ну назначили
initially how did he get there he was the
изначально как он туда он же был
president of Georgia and then How did he get there he
президент Грузии а потом Как попал
received Ukrainian citizenship and
получил украинское гражданство и
everything that is again
всё то есть опять
he
же он туда
came there that is Figuratively ruined his country there
приехал то есть Свою страну образно там
some kind of this and came to Ukraine
развалил какие-то это и приехал на Укра
Yes and came to ruin Yes and came to
Да и пришёл развалить Да и пришёл
ruin the Odessa region Yes you are
развалить одесскую область Да вы
right Well and how did they allow this
правы Ну а как допустили это
how did they allow this well The thing is that
как допустили это ну Дело в том что
look do you agree that since de Pergo
смотри ты согласен что с де перго года
the Anglo-Saxons have been ruining Russia they
англосаксы разваливают Россию они
ruined the Soviet Union and so on Yes then
развалили Советский Союз так и дальше Да
they want to ruin everything else it
дальше они хотят развалить всё остальное
all started with the fact that Yeltsin and
вот всё началось с того что Ельцин и
Gorbachev as the protege of the Anglo-Saxons
Горбачёв как ставленник англосаксов
ruined the Soviet Union into 15
развалили Советский Союз на 15
Slavic republics Estonia Latvia
славянских республик Эстония Латвия
wait a minute So here's what the plans are
сечас подожди Так вот и дальше по планах
If you know the Marshall Plan, yes,
Если ты знаешь План Маршала такой да вот
and the Dalis plan and the Alice plan about the collapse of the
и план далиса и план Алиса о развале
republics further than all the others, they wanted to collapse
дальше всех республик они захотели
Russia, they wanted to collapse Georgia,
развалить Россию они захотели развалить
collapse Ukraine And the other
Грузию развалить Украину Да и остальные
republics, that's why Saakashvili is their
Республики поэтому Саакашвили как ихний
Agent First, he collapsed Georgia when
Агент Сначала он развалил Грузию когда
Georgia was already
Грузия уже была
collapsed Saakashvili was transferred here so that
развалена Саакашвили перебросили сюда
he would collapse Ukraine That is,
чтобы он развалил Украину Вот то есть
this is a very clear plan You understand
это очень чёткий план Ты же понимаешь
that the Anglo-Saxons need to
что англосаксов нужно
collapse the entire USSR to the end, right down to the
развалить весь СССР до конца прямо до
smallest ones Yes, the Anglo-Saxons,
маленьких-маленьких Да вот англосакс вот
since the times of Kievan Rus, yes,
ещё со времён Руси Киевской да
the Anglo-Saxons have always been haunted by the
англосаксов всегда не давало покоя
Slavic Brotherhood because only
Славянское Братство потому что только
united Slavs We have always been,
объединённые славяне Мы же всегда были
always We were all Slavs in one state
всегда Мы в одном государстве были все
Serbs, Ukrainians, Chechens, there
славяне Сербы украинцы чеченцы там
Buryats All of us, Slavic brothers,
буряты Все мы братья славяне были против
fought against Hitler, well, really, well, yes, yes And
Гитлера воевали ну правда ну да да И
when our Slavic grandfathers, yes, these
когда наши деды славянские да Этим
Anglo-Saxons over the Reichstag  they raised the
англосаксов над Рейхстагом водрузили
Victory Banner, they didn't forget, they were
Знамя Победы то они не забыли они
offended by us, they were offended and they
обиделись на нас они обиделись и они
said, We'll go another way, we
сказали Мы пойдём другим путём мы
destroyed your USSR, they couldn't defeat the
развали ваш СССР они не смогли победить
USSR by war, and they decided that they would go and
СССР войной и они решили что они пойдут
introduce
будут внедрять в Правительство СССР и
various Anglo-Saxons into the Government of the USSR and the republics, and if you
республик разных англосаксов и если ты
look, Well, agree that Yeltsin had
посмотришь Ну согласись что у Ельцина
some kind of atypical face, it was true, not like the
какой-то нетипичное лицо было правда не
average
похожее на среднестатистического
Russian, he seemed too drunk, so to speak,
русского слишком пьяный он такой как бы
True, So what, Yes, yes, Yeltsin,
Правда Ну и что Да так вот да Ельцин
Yeltsin, he's Russian, you only know
Ельцин он русский только по маме знаешь
who his father is from his mother, did you look at his biography, his father is a
кто его Папа ты смотрел биографию его
Jew? There's nothing worse. Well, I know that he's from the Urals, from
евреи Нет хуже Ну я знаю что он с Урала
somewhere there, so that's right,
откуда-то там так так вот да отец
Yeltsin's father, uh, a British lord from Wales. Yes,
Ельцина э британский лорд из э Уэльса Да
uh, Lord Bacon, so he's in the Urals. When it
ээ Лорд бекон так вот он на Урале Когда
was
было
after 1945, when
в после сорок пятого года когда была
Britain was together with the Soviet Union, uh,
Британия вместе с с советским союзом ээ
they had an agreement on the construction of
было у них договор о отстройки
enterprises, and the British worked at the
предприятий и британцы работали на
enterprises. Yes, Lord Bacon, in
предприятиях Да Лорд бекон в
Yekaterinburg, that's exactly when it was  there was also
Екатеринбурге как раз тогда это ещё был
Sverdlovsk, he was in charge of the metallurgical
Свердловск э руководил металлургическим
enterprise, he
предприятием обустройством он тогда
met Nina Yeltsin, he was a
познакомился с Ниной ельциной вот
simple worker, she was a crane operator at the
простой рабочий она была крановщица на
plant, and they had a connection, as if to
заводе и у них произошел так как бы
say something that didnt exist in the Soviet Union,
говоря то чего в Советском Союзе не было
and then Lord Bacon was sent
конект и потом Лорда бекона отправили
back to Britain, yes, so look at the
назад в Британию да Так посмотри в
biography in the Yeltsin Center, like even this is there,
биографии в Ельцин центре типа даже это
and he took, it turns out, he was born without a
есть и он взял он родился получается без
father, he took his mothers surname Yeltsin
отца у него он взял фамилию мамы Ельцин
because his mother, Nina Yeltsin, was a simple
потому что мама Нина Ельцина простая
crane operator. And note that Yeltsin had
крановщица Вот И заметь что Ельцин Ни
never been to Britain, he was referring
одного раза не был в Британии был обозн
to his dad, who had thrown him out, what did he
на своего папу который его кинул что он
say? Im not going to Britain, but
сказал я в Британию не ногой но
British aristocratic circles. Yes, they
британские аристократические круги
found a way to him, they say you have
Да нашли к нему выход говорят в тебе
our
есть наша
blood. Lets
кровь Давай мы будем вместе с тобой
move him together toward success. They promoted him to success.
двигать к успеху его продвинули к успеху
Yes, they promoted him up the career
Да его там продвинули по карьерной
ladder, they bribed someone, thats all, and
лестнице кого-то подкупили кого-то всё и
hes already the head of the Supreme Soviet of the
он так хоп уже глава Верховного Совета
RSFSR, then, hop, hes already like on  tre stands
РСФСР потом хоп он уже типа на тре стоит
together with Zolotov and is already shouting against
вместе с золотовым и уже кричит против
Gorbachev that the USSR is not needed and that's all and everything
Горбачёва что сссра не надо и всё и всё
Anglo-Saxons have a very simple strategy
англосакс очень просто у них стратегия
they have been doing for centuries how they
такая они с давних веков делали как они
impregnate Slavic women so that
оплодотворять славянских женщин чтоб от
they give birth
них рожали
here the Armed Forces are very simple Gorbachev, you
тут ВС очень просто Горбачёв тоже ты
know, is also not really a
знаешь не совсем из
Slav Listen, there are many who are in power who are
славян Слушай много же кто у власти
not
сидит не
Russians in principle there are no Russians so if you
русские принципе нет русских так если
think about it I'm saying in Russia
подумать Я же говорю в России
everyone is a Jew Yes Zelensky is a Jew Yes Medvedev is a
все еврей Да Зеленский еврей Да Медведев
Jew Putin is a Jew here Anglo-Saxons Jews
еврей Путин еврей тут англосакс евреи
only talk about the World Cup their own people Yes they
только это о ЧМ говорит своих провит Да
promote their own people like that look they have such an
так своих продвигают смотри у них такая
idea Yes maybe you know the concept of the
идея Да может ты знаешь концепция
golden billion
золотого миллиарда
m I've heard No no I haven't heard No they want
м Слышал Не не не слышал Нет они хотят
Yes leave a billion people so that
Да оставить э миллиард людей чтобы на
only Anglo-Saxons remain on earth for
земле остались только англосаксы для
this they need to clear the earth of
этого им нужно очистить землю от
Slavs because the Slavs have the most
славян потому что у славян самая
fertile land in the world you
плодородная земля в мире ты же это
know this black soil All Germans You know that
знаешь чернозёмы Все немцы Ты знаешь что
during the war the Germans took black soil and
немцы во время войны брали чернозём и
exported it by the trainload until I forgot to say a
вагонами вывозили пока не забыл сказать
billion to
миллиард
leave purely Anglo-Saxons on the planet
оставить на планете чисто англосаксов
Anglo-Saxons Yes and the rest
англосаксов Да а остальных
so that there are none and the rest there will be no one
чтобы нет а остальных никого не будет
or only they will be Yes because they
или только они будут Да потому что они
believe
считают
that what what they will do to live they
что что что они будут делать жить они
believe that for now let's
считают что для теперь
say this minute ecological
скажем сею минутного экологического
state yes for the earth it is comfortable 1 billion
состояния да для земли комфортно 1 млрд
population and overpopulation of the planet
населения и пере население планеты
negatively affects resources for
негативно влияет на ресурсы для
consumption of Anglo-Saxons Yes they do not have enough of
потребления англосаксов Да им не хватает
all sorts of rare earth metals and so
всяких редкоземельных металлов и так
on Yes because then everyone
дальше Да потому что каждому тогда
needs a phone from this billion and that's it
телефон нужен из этого миллиарда и всё
Therefore it will be like this there will be poor
Поэтому вот будет так будут бедные
Anglo-Saxons rich Anglo-Saxons but
англосаксы богатые англосаксы но
only Anglo-Saxons will remain and they will
останутся только англосаксы и будут
resettle in the captured territories You
расселять по захваченным территориям Ты
know our ancestors Slavic Aryans Yes they
же знаешь наши предки Славяно Арии Да
lived here and since time immemorial we are all Slavs
тут жили и покон веков мы все славяне
our Svarog Perun there it all was is and
наш там Сварог перун это всё было есть и
will be well so let's return to the question of
будет ну так давайте вернёмся к вопросу
Russia attacking Ukraine What
того что Россия напала на Украину Какое
Look this is all I will explain to you it is
Смотри это уже всё я тебе объясню это
all a consequence of a large chain of
всё следствие большой цепочки череды
events from the collapse of the USSR it is all Yeltsin and
событий из развала СССР это всё Ельцин и
Gorbachev protege of the Anglo-Saxons it was they who
Горбачёв ставленник англосаксов это они
did Now everything is going on as usual
сделали Теперь всё идёт своим чередом
here as you know for example take a
вот ты как знаешь например возьми
snowball throw  from the mountain Yes and that's it, it's already
снежный ком кинь с горы Да и вс он уже
rolling you just threw it and it's rolling it's
катится ты уже только кинул а он катится
already predetermined it's physics Yes the law of
это уже предрешено это физика Да закон
universal gravitation and nothing more so
всемирного тяготения и больше ничего так
here Yeltsin and Gorbachev let the Genie out
и тут Ельцин и горбачов выпустили Джина
of the bottle And as every Russian knows
из бутылки А как Каждый русский знает
if the bottle is already open Yes until everything is
если бутылка уже открыта Да пока вс не
finished there will be
закончи будет
movement now this Genie it was released it was
движ сейчас этот Джин он выпущен он
released and it is now absorbing the minds of
выпущен и он сейчас поглощает умы
Russians and there is nothing you can do about it
россиян и тут уже ничего не сделаешь
this snowball must roll to
этот снежный ком должен докатиться до
its opinion By the way as
своего мнения Кстати как говорил
Zarathustra said yes what Not everyone will understand what
заратустра да что Не каждый поймёт то
everyone understands this is a very, very
что понимает каждый это очень-очень
important concept and it is now being
важная концепция и она сейчас
implemented in Russia itself That's how
реализуется собственно в России Вот
And how do you do it the same
так А у вас как она делается тоже самое
Yes we are part of the former
Да мы ж часть бывшего
Anglo-Saxon to us the same thing does it
нам англосакс то самое
mean that as originally
де это же не значит что как изначально
on your television
по вашему телевидению
FDM or whatever the
фдм или как о называется
channel Rossi is called that's right Yes the Anglo-Saxon is
канал Росси правильно Да англосакс
doing it on purpose This is again propaganda is going on That's
специально делаю Это же опять Пропаганда
right yes yes they are propagandizing the Anglo-Saxon to
идёт Правильно же да да они англосакс
me you know the question
пропагандируют мне вот Знаете вопрос
Yes what Ukraine
Да что Украина
Russia tore out the toilet and sent it home Well
Россия вырывал туалет и отправлял домой
really that much Yes it's brutal
Ну неужели настолько Да это жесть это
I understand it's awful of course there well well they don't
жесть я понимаю конечно там ну ну не и
understand that people are going there there's no
понимают то что люди едут там никакой
Motherland nothing it's all clear everyone is
там Родины ничего это всё понятно все
going there for their own selfish reasons Well again
едут там из своих корыстных там Ну опять
money Well you have the same Well you have it
же деньги Ну у вас также Ну у вас там
somehow like that the same TCK let's say it
как-нибудь вот то же тцк у вас допустим
works for you Well again they show on the Internet
работает Ну опять же по интернету же
how people are taken away let's say It's the
показывают как людей забирают допустим
same as you What do you think look
Это же как ты Как ты считаешь смотри
Russia is the richest country there is gas oil
Россия богатейшая страна есть газ нефть
gold diamonds How does it happen that
золото алмазы Да как так получается что
the Anglo-Saxons take all these
англосаксы забирают все эти себе ваши
resources of yours and you have nothing left and you
ресурсы и вам ничего не остаётся и вы
live in poverty as I think yes And how should it
живёте как считаю я это да А как должно
be
быть
How should it be Well your resources should
Как должно быть Ну ваши ресурсы должны
remain with you and you should be
оставаться у вас и вы должны быть
rich like in
богачами как в
Dubai Well most
Дубаях Ну скорее всего
likely probably Well again
наверное Ну опять же вот
figuratively the same loans Yes there at high
образно те же кредиты Да там под большие
interest rates they are not given out just like that yes how does it
проценты это же не просто так даются да
happen that the Anglo-Saxons
да как так получается что англосаксы да
take all your
забирают все ваши
resources Well how does it happen that
ресурсы Ну как получается правительстве
people are sitting in the government Yes and they dictate and that's it, that is, it turns out well the
сидят люди Да вот и диктуют и всё то
Anglo-Saxons
есть получается ну Путину англосаксы
tell Putin give it to us Everything in short
говорят отдавай нам Всё короче
yes Well probably it turns out that way that is it  it
да Ну наверное получается так то есть
turns out Putin is also a protg of the
получается Путин тоже ставленник
Anglo-Saxons Stalin is not Stalin if you do such
англосаксов Сталин не Сталин если такие
things then he is not
дела делать значит он как бы не
against it Well, how about here again I
против Ну а как здесь опять же я образно
speak figuratively Yes there for 7000 Granny's
говорю Да там за 7000 У бабульки
gas is cut off, let's say yes Well, and someone
отрезают газ допустим да Ну а у кого-то
there has a billion and there, let's say, nothing
там миллиард и их там допустим ничего
again this covers them up well no not
опять же это прикрывает их же ну не не
just the same
просто так же
right Yes, and you also have work What do
правильно Да также у вас работа Что у
you have corruption You have the first in the country
вас коррупция У вас же первый по стране
or how much
или сколько там
corruption there is Yes, we generally have well we do not have
коррупционные Да у нас вообще ну у нас
corruption because we already have
нет коррупции потому что мы уже подк
our entire territory You know that according to
всю нашу территорию Ты же знаешь что по
British maritime law Yes, Ukraine
британскому морскому праву Да Украина
is considered the sea shelf and belongs to the
считается шельф моря и принадлежит
British
британской
Crown So what are we fighting for then We are
Короне А так за что тогда
all We are slaves of the crown we can't we we are
воюете мы всё Мы рабы короны мы не можем
ordinary people What did they tell
мы мы простые люди нам что нам сказали
us The British put a president in our hands You
Нам бриты поставили президента Вы же вы
can't go out against your president
не можете против своего президента выйти
no you have power and that's it the power
нет у вас есть власть и всё власть вам
told you you go You are a simple little
сказала вы идёте Вы простой маленький
man you have no influence on anything the same thing with
человек вы на ничто не влияете так же и
us the British put
у нас нам британцы поставили
Zelensky in our hands he is the same Well, you know his
Зеленского он же Ну ты знаешь его
real last name who Zelensky is not in
настоящая фамилия кого Зеленского нет
the NFL I didn't know  I was
НФЛ не знал
n't even interested Yes, this is in
я не интересовался даже да это в
translation Yes, Zelensky did it And according to
переводе Да сделали Зеленский А по
his passport, he has a passport Yes, it says there, yes,
паспорту у него паспорт Да там написано
Mar
да Мар
Greenfields, no one voted What
гринфилдс никто не голосовал Какие
elections Well, you would know in Russia how
выборы Ну ты же в России бы знаешь как
elections are made, they wrote there and that's it There are no elections Do
выборы делаются там написали и
you believe that
всё Никаких выборов нету Ты веришь что
somewhere in the world there are
где-то в мире есть
elections Well, at the moment I don't believe it anymore, I don't believe it
выборы Ну на данный момент я уже не верю
anywhere Look, it's the
не верю нигде нет это Смотри это
Anglo-Saxons who create the illusion of democracy Yes, they do it
англосаксы делают иллюзию демократии да
there, the Russians, look, it seems like
делают там россияне смотрите вроде как
elections Putin is with us, look, they did it there, it
выборы Путин у нас смотрите сделали там
seems like there's a stadium, so a stadium Oops, they
вроде как там стадион так стадион Опа
drew such a number and that's it Would you
всё нарисовали такую количество и всё ты
believe that a guy who played the
поверишь что мужик который играл на на
piano could win the
рояле смог бы победить в
elections Well, you've had many presidents,
выборах Ну у вас много президентов были
such incomprehensible No, well, all this is
такие непонятные Не ну так вот всё это
all the Anglo-Saxons are putting this up It's such a joke, you
всё англосакс ставят это же Прикол такой
know,
понимаешь
they're just laughing stupidly, they're like that Let's
ожени тупо угорают они такие-то Давай
put
поставим
hats on them He stole, like they drew
им шапки воровал типа нарисовали ему
elections for him, victory, we're like that Well, okay, the
выборы победу мы такие Ну ладно нам
Anglo-Saxons gave us what are we going to do then,
англосаксы дали что мы сделаем потом
the Anglo-Saxons made Maidan or something and they
англосакс сделали Майдан что-то и
didn't take Yanukovych  they put in Poroshenko,
Янукович не взяли поставили Порошенко
stupidly, in short, who owns a chocolate factory. Imagine.
тупо короче который шоколадную фабрику
Go make candy for people, make candy for
Прикинь Иди делай людям конфеты делай
children. In short, they didn't put him in as
детям Короче не его поставили
president after that they didn't like him. They
президентом после этого не понравился Он
took him. In short, they did it. They put in a
им взяли анса короче сделали поставили
game called Naro.
вой игра Наро
And how did Zelensky end up in
а как как Зеленский получается вообще в
this structure? As I'm telling you,
эту структуру попал как я я тебе говорю
look, because he's Greenfeld, yes,
смотри потому что он гринфельд да
Greenfeld, he has some kind of connection
гринфельд он э имеет какое-то отношение
to the British Crown. He has a second
к британской Короне у него троюродный
cousin. He's a second cousin. He's one of the British
брат троюродный брат так из британских
aristocrats. And the British
аристократов и его британская
aristocracy somehow decided that they
аристократия как-то вышила решила что им
needed a president who would not only be
нужен уже президент который не просто
appointed by him, but who would at least
будет да назначен им А который ещё
be connected to them somehow. And they
как-то хоть будет с ними связано и они
took him. This Waldemar Greenfeld never
взяли Вот это Вальдемар гринфин же не
lived. Look, he never lived in Ukraine before.
жил смотри он же не жил в Украине раньше
He only came to Ukraine to give
он только приезжал в Украину делать
concerts. This desto pi quarter. He's a British
концерты вот этот десто пй квартал он
citizen. He didn't have a
подданный Великобритании у него не было
Ukrainian passport before the Maidan. After the
украинского паспорта до Майдана после
Maidan, the British might have wanted to make him one right away,
Майдана британцы они его может сразу
but he didn't have a
хотели сделать но у него ещё не было
passport yet. They made Poroshenko Poroshenko for him.
паспорта сделали Порошенко Порошенко ему
issued citizenship of Ukraine back then if
выдал гражданство Украины ещё тогда если
maybe watched was this Dep quarter
может смотрел было этот Деп квартал
Poroshenko came then was already
Порошенко пришёл тогда уже был
president Yes came to visit in deno py
президентом Да пришёл в гости в дено пй
quarter and on stage solemnly handed
квартал и на сцене торжественно вручил
this Zelensky a passport of Ukraine you
этому зеленскому паспорт Украины
know and that's it he did it to his own detriment
понимаешь и всё он тогда это на свою
Poroshenko and then Ang sak
голову сделал Порошенко и тогда Анг сак
such Opa everything Zelensky Now a citizen of
такие Опа всё Зеленский Теперь гражданин
Ukraine he can formally make him
Украины он его можно формально поставить
president made president that's all Well
президентом поставили президентом вот и
what can you do here we are ordinary
всё Ну и что тут сделаешь мы простые
people we don't influence anything we are small you
люди мы ни на что не влияем мы маленькие
know we are small squeakers in this like
понимаешь мы маленькие пищики в этом как
you do you influence something in
и ты ты влияешь на что-то в
Russia No I'm talking about this T you see And
России Нет я про это говорю Т видишь И
we don't influence you tomorrow the Anglo-Saxons
мы не влияем тебе завтра англосаксы
will make Zhirinovsky dead they will say he is
поставят Жириновского мёртвого скажут он
dead but he will be your President and
Мёртвый но он будет у вас Президент и
what will you do You won't go to the
что вы сделаете Вы же не выйдете на
rally Well now how does it turn out what are you
митинг Ну теперь как получается за что
fighting for we are ordinary people we are not in for anything
воюете вы мы простые люди мы ни за что
we are pawns in this and you are a pawn we are all
не во мы пешки в это и ты пешка мы все
pawns there are
пешки есть в мире
488 people in the world these are families that
правят 488 человек это семьи которые
rule the world they are the Armed Forces  we decide we are just
правят миром они ВС решают мы просто
pawns on this chessboard they play
пешки на этой шахматной доске играют они
we are expendable material these
мы расходный материал вот этот
1488 people Bilderberg club they
1488 людей бильдербергский клуб они всё
decide everything they have access to resources they
решают у них доступ к ресурсам у них они
nominate all the presidents they
выставляют всех президентов они
pass all the
принимают все
laws you are streaming Yes no And what do I
законы вы Стрим идёте Да нет А что
just communicate with people Well I think
просто общаюсь с людьми Ну я думаю
stream no you don't record Because
стрими нет ты не записываешь Потому что
if you post it of course it will be
если ты выложишь мне конечно будет
hard for me here in
тяжело тут в
Ukraine no You are joking I can see that you are
Украине нет Ты шутишь Я же вижу что ты
playing along well no exactly that's what
подыгрывает ну как нет именно так что
confused you in that long conversation
тебя за смущало в том длинном разговоре
we had I do you think you are a fool I
который мы Я же что ты думаешь дурак я
can see how you started communicating differently From
вижу как ты начал общаться по-другому С
what
какого
moment Well from that moment I saw and
момента Ну с такого момента я же смот и
you started talking differently what do I
ты по-другому начал разговаривать что я
not understand or what okay from the
не понимаю что ли или что ладно с
moment when I said that
момента когда я говорил что зеленскому
Poroshenko gave Zelensky a passport I was
Порошенко дал паспорт Это я
joking I didn't do that I already understood from the conversation You are talking
пошутил я не это я уже понял по разговор
something You are no longer like that I didn't
Гово что-то Ты уже не так Я уже не стал
tell you anymore
тебе говорить
but
но как бы
somehow you changed differently you
так по-другому поменялся ты по-другому
speak differently it's obvious
говоришь это же видно
Everything It just seems to me that you recorded me and then he will
Всё Мне просто кажется что ты меня запис
post it
ито выложит
here you are now joking again Here
вот ты сейчас Опять шутишь Вот
100% and where am I going to post Well, I dont
100% и куда я тея буду выкладывать Ну я
know, I already had something I talked
не знаю у меня уже было Я что-то говорил
to your bloggers and I had a little bit
с вашими блогерами и мне немножко было
of this No, are you kidding now I
из этого нет ты сейчас прикалываешься я
know this is 100% a joke on your part but
знаю это 100% прикол с твоей стороны но
its a stupid joke Ill
это глупый прикол Я тебе
tell you the meaning of this joke I just dont
скажу смысл этого прикола Я просто не
understand Youre sitting under the flag, youre
понимаю Ты же сидишь под флагом
definitely rooting for your country, thats
однозначно топишь за свою страну
right, so whats your
правильно соответственно у тебя какая
mission to prove Tell your viewers,
миссия доказать Сказать своим зрителям
subscribers, to tell Look,
подписчикам рассказать вот смотрите
whats this and that and I dont have
Какой такой такой так же а у меня
any flags I Understand,
никаких ни флагов нету я Понимаете вот
you are such patriots who have flags
вы патриоты такие которые вот флаги у
hanging figuratively Yes Listen, heres the
вас висят образно Да Слушай а вот такой
question Why do you go out to
вопрос вопрос Зачем ты выходишь в чет
chat on Roulette, Im talking to you
пообщаться вот с тобой общаюсь
No, look I dont have a specific goal
Нет смотрите У меня нет конкретной цели
Like you Yes, youre sitting there specifically rooting
Как у вас Да вы сидите конкретно топите
for this and everything and it makes no difference to you
там да за это за всё и вам без разницы
there, yes, there, thats exactly how you have it
там да там именно вот так у вас
set up, some
поставленная вот э какая-то тема
specific topic because of this there Say I
конкретна из за этого там Говорите Я же
understand all this perfectly well
понимаю
if you want me to be  with you
вот если хочешь чтобы я был с тобой
sezen I will tell Yes I am a propagandist
сезен я расскажу Да я пропагандист
Yes I am a propagandist Look I work for the
Да я пропагандист смотри я работаю на
American
американский
bastard Our task is to develop
гаде Наша задача входит развивать
Russophobia among Ukrainians Yes Hatred towards
русофобию среди украинцев Да Ненависть к
Russians it has started again I know there is not a
россиянам это опять начали Я знаю вот
single truth in your words This is
ваших словах ни одной нету Правды это
serious I am telling you No Well
серьёзно Я тебе говорю Нет ну вот вот
look again Why This is honest
смотрите опять Для чего Это честная
Pioneer about
Пионерская про
Well you just
Ну просто ты меня
deciphered me No what kind of intelligence officer
расшифровал нет какой какой разведчик
will say that I am an intelligence officer Well this is stupid Sola
скажет что я разведчик Ну это глупо Сола
but no You know what the joke is When you
а нет Знаешь в чём прикол Ты когда
say that you Intelligence officers and they dont
говоришь что ты Разведчики и тебе не
believe you and then everything is okay You see you
верят и тогда всё окей Ты же видишь ты
again Well what is the point of trying to pry some information out of me
опять Вот ну смысл выпытывать от меня
Well this is stupid
какие-то информации Ну это глупо потому
because I dont know anything Well in fact Well you are
что я ничего не знаю ну по факту Ну ты
like you know joking there Yes there they
так типа знаешь прикалываешься там да
write on people like Can I
там пишут на люди типа Можно
joke around or something Yes there I
прикольнуться или что-то Да там я так
understand because With your gaze You are
понимаю потому что Взглядом Ты
peeping there in the chat or somewhere Well
подсматривает там в чат или куда-то Ну
it is all visible yes no well you are not
видно же это всё да нет ну не так
looking like that But it is not for nothing that
смотришь а по-другому
you have  the flag is hanging Why if
не зря У тебя вот флаг висит Зачем если
you just went out to chat Not in vain Not in vain
ты просто вышел общаться Не зря не зря
You are not such a Patriot that there
Ты не такой Патриот чтобы там
really there well to the end you can hop bribe
действительно там ну до конца тебя можно
do it this way you will do it
хоп подкупить делай так ты будешь делать
this way and you understand the whole point of
так вот и весь смысл понимаешь твоего
your patriotism or there I don't know so
твоего патриотизма или там я не знаю так
look what patriotism I'm telling you
смотри какой патриотизм Я же тебе говорю
I'm on the salary of the State Department they pay me to
я на зарплате у госдепа мне платят
develop Russophobia I
развивают русофобию я
develop Well Develop you see
развиваю Ну Развивай видишь развиваю
I develop Look I'll say so some people still
Смотри я скажем так люди некоторые ещё
think damn like Russia is a friend like
думают блин вроде Россия друг вроде
neutral And I'm
нейтрально А я им
digging into them to hate Russia Let's Russia is an
впиваются ненавидеть Россию Давайте
enemy Russia is an enemy Yes pay me for this
Россия враг Россия враг Да мне за это
Look you hammer it in like this
плати Смотри вот ты вот так вбиваешь Да
What did they hate And what do you get out of
что ненавидели И что в этом получаешь от
this Well I get I get a salary from the
этого Ну я получаю Я получаю зарплату от
State Department I don't care what the
госдепа мне всё равно для чего это
State Department is for I'm a simple person my business I
госдеп я простой человек моё дело я
did the job this is my job how to
сделал работу это моя работа дальше как
live next why do I live I spend this money
жить зачем я живу я эти деньги трачу Да
Well live with lies yes it's normal This is
ну с враньём жить да это нормально Это
my job Well someone kills people in
это моя работа Ну кто-то убивает людей в
Ukraine and someone deceives Russia  What
Украине а кто-то обманывает Росси Что
is clear, it is clear that you live But
понятно понятно что ты живёшь А вот
other people, like, well, look, this
другие люди как бы ну смотри это этот
world is selfish Yes, this is my job, I am
мир эгоистичный Да это моя работа я
just doing my
просто исполняю свою
job, it is stupid I just
работу это глупо Я просто с тобой
talked to you, for example, it does not mean that you
допустим пообщался это не значит что ты
hammered into me this, you understand No, you are
мне вбил в эту понимаешь Нет так ты
just knowledgeable Look, I hammer into
просто ты знающий Смотри я вбиваю
others, I understand perfectly well how it
другим я прекрасно понимаю как это
works, well, not what specifically Well,
работает ну не то что конкретно Ну
on top of that, I still
поверх я всё-таки всё равно понимаю
understand somewhere, somehow, you understand, I am not saying
где-то что-то как-то понимаете не говорю
that everything is good there in Russia or
что там в России всё хорошо там или
somehow, this is not the question, it is all
как-то это вопрос не в этом это всё
clear Yes, it is not good everywhere, but the point
понятно да это везде нег хорошо но смысл
is that if something happened in Russia,
в том что вот если в России случилось о
look, some house exploded there, it
смотрите там взорвался же дом какой-то
means it is not so, but if something explodes in America,
значит не так а если в Америке что-то
you will not even say a word about
взорвётся вы даже слово не скажете об
it You see, that is why, yes You
этом понимаете Вот жем зачем да Вот
see, what is the point It is clear that
видите В чём смысл Понятно везде есть
everywhere, everywhere, somewhere, something is happening, but it is
везде ве где-то что-то творится но это
presented in a completely different way I do not understand
преподносится совсем по-другому я пони
one person in any way, you beat their
одному человеку по-любому во бьёшь
head in there, there it is like that It is
голову там образом там это так Это
clear,
понятно
but I think which person understands Well
но я думаю который человек понимает Ну
more or less I understand that if a person
более-менее я понимаю что человеку если
says that you are a fool, a fool, a fool, you will
говорит что ты дурак дурак дурак ты
say Well really I may be a fool,
скажешь Ну действительно Я может дурак
as it were, yes it is all clear it is stupid it is
как бы да это всё понятно это глупо
just stupid to hammer in that now
просто это глупо вбивать что сейчас
Russia is an enemy well how is it an enemy
Россия Враг ну как она враг
and others others who did this they are not
а другие другие кто это сделал они не
enemies it turns out yes the same Look I will say
враги получается да таже Смотри я скажу
I do not understand
я в политике не разбираюсь я не
politics I am not interested in politics I do not need this I
интересуюсь политикой Мне это не нужно Я
work You specifically on these topics immediately m
работаю Ты конкретно на эти темы сразу м
say Who is to blame yes look I don't care who is to blame I get
говоришь Кто виноват да смотри мне всё
paid for the fact that I
равно кто виноват Мне платят за то что я
promote this all yes I got paid
вот это продвигаю всё да Мне заплатили
this is my job you work you are a plumber yes
это моя работа ты работаешь ты сантехник
Or Yes someone goes signs a
да Или Да кто-то идёт подписывает
contract kills people in Ukraine yes And I
контракт убивает людей в Украине да А я
just cultivate hatred towards
просто вот Воспитываю Ненависть к
Russians Well this is my job Just
россиянам Ну это моя работа Just
business No it is wrong your job Well
бизнес Нет неправильно твоя работа Ну
why Well look if there is someone there a
почему Ну смотри если есть кто-то там
private military company wipes the
частная военная компания стирает с лица
city of Bakhmut off the face of the city 70,000 population Yes
города город бахмут 70.000 населения Да
this is their job They just take a
это ихняя работа Они просто берут
salary and work and I develop
зарплату и работают а я развиваю
Russophobia is my job I do It's
русофобию это моя работа я делаю Это
high quality I love my job I get paid
качественно Я люблю свою работу Мне за
well for it And I
это платят хорошо платят Да и я
enjoy it you know how we had
наслаждаюсь знаешь как вот у нас был
Grigory Skovoroda, a philosopher, he had
Григорий Сковорода философ он
this concept akin Prat, like a kind of
такое понятие вёл сродна Прат типа как
akin work, the one that you just like,
бы сродный труд тот что тебе как раз по
find something you like to do I
душе найди себе дело по душе я нашёл
really found it and I look in this world everyone
реально и я смотри в этом мире каждый
earns as much as they can, how can I
зарабатывает как может как может я
honestly do it I honestly do my work
честно делаю Я честно свой труд дела
the Anglo-Saxons pay me for it and I keep records Yes,
мне англосаксы платят за это и я отчёты
how many people have I talked to Yes,
веду Да сколько я людей поговорил Да
how much Russophobia have I developed and that's it And
сколько русофобии развил и
how do you know about it, how much have
всё А как ты об этом знаешь что сколько
you done it, how do you understand I
ты сделал это как ты понимаешь я
keep a table Yes, for example, some don't
табличку веду Да некоторые например не
just communicate Yes, I contribute and I take their
просто общаюсь Да я вношу а я беру у них
contacts and then they contact them there too I come up with
контакты да потом с ними ещё там
what to
контактируют в голову что
do in Russia, for example,
сделать в России такое что-то например
something with a transformer or with a
там с трансформатором или с
hang The Internet couldn't handle it,
завис Не выдержал интернет
so like, subscribe, comment Bang, write to
так лайк подписка комент Бах пись на й
Telegram right now, axis VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok, that's very good  very respectfully YouTube has taken
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg Orcs in your ban and even
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
richer videos dont show people often dont
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we can Mali operational link drink
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок пи
right now and Popik there in telegram
ться прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми
okrim video also tsikava and korisna
окрим видео ще теж е цикава и корисна
information and we are guilty of you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
Nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write a
пиши а